John Bergsen

123 Bedford Avenue, New York, NY, 12345 John bergsen (©example.com {123)456-7890

PROFILE

A Pizza Delivery Driver with four years of experience specializing in product delivery, customer service, communication, and route navigation. A proven track record of identifying opportunities to improve on-time delivery rates during high-volume business hours.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Pizza Delivery Driver

Giorgio's, New York, NY | May 2019- Present

- Execute food and beverage deliveries to 30+ residential customers per day, ensure on-time delivery during high traffic periods, and ensure accuracy of product orders
- Maintain knowledge of all menu items and food products and interface with customers to identify resolutions to quality issues
- Plan and navigate complex routes and identify opportunities to optimize planning to reduce average delivery times by 15% for customers

Pizza Delivery Driver

9th Street Pizza, New York, NY | June 2018 - May 2019

- Managed a variety of food delivery orders for an Italian pizza restaurant and navigated a variety of traffic and weather conditions while maintaining a 90% on-time delivery rating
- Maintained the safety and cleanliness of company vehicles and ensured compliance with company policies and food handling protocols

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

Central Park East Central High School, New York, NY September 2014 - June 2018

KEY SKILLS

- Product Delivery
- ♦ Route Planning
- Safe Driving
- Customer Service
- Communication